I love this thing with real
and look how much I have in my account
thank you brother
bro calls me here quickly so we can exchange this idea
do this accounting
then the financial is on
i have to get this whole amount of brownie
that I sold
that's just the cost
outside we share the profit is that
because i call you there
ah I'll pack
I will give 1 party
I will play 1 whore
caraca now comes o
tax
logistics
supplier
society
box
packaging
ah stop all brother
and 1 merrequinha left here for us
six thousand nine hundred and fifty reais in the uncle account
let's pay the bill now
let enter here ó
click here on management in the Cora application
and then you come here o payment link
you can control everything you paid for
that is open
you can see that here we still have 600 reals left for me to get
in the square
was sold
1260 brownies
factory only
my brother
I have three thousand seven hundred and eighty reais
out profit no bro
because it's half to half
then seven five hundred and sixty
Than the six hundred reais I have to receive
see three less
seven hundred and eighty
three seven hundred and eighty left
malandro
exactly
the profit money
but divided
for two
that's my profit bro
this is what i'm doing is just a sales channel bro
I need to create a strategy to diversify
multiple sales channels
it's on me
I think I had an idea
bro I just did the accounting here in a hurry
one thousand two hundred and sixty grams
it's not bad no bro
I have an idea here
top of joining me on this too
it's one hundred percent easy to say
any idea can
send it
so stop is as follows
we will